# Sakamoto Seiji

## Software engineer



### About me

I am a full stack developer with 6 years of experience in IT. Exactly, I have +4 years of web and mobile development experience and +2 years of blockchain development experience.

I have a hobby in program development and work hard to learn new skills. I love coding so much that it can be said that coding is everything in my life.

As a developer who dreams of high-quality and wonderful coding, I hope that my program will be a wonderful thing that helps people.

I am familiar with building clean, efficient, well-documented, well-structured, high-quality code projects. Also, I am very well-versed in the agile approach in project development and really love to add my creativity to the overall project implementation.

My focus is on clean, elegant, and efficient codes and I am able to work on new and existing micro-sites, landing pages, templates, and provide guidance and troubleshooting support to clients.

Thank you for viewing my profile, hope we can work on a project together soon.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Emai

sakamotoseiji100@gmail.com

**Telegram** 

https://t.me/bestblockchaindevelop

**GitHub** 

https://github.com/sakamotoseiji100

Skype

live:.cid.57323f23b950525a

**Address** 

United States, Honolulu

### **Experience**

December 2019 - March 2022 **Sotatek** 

March 2019 - October 2019 ChatPlus Co., Ltd.

December 2017 - October 2019 **C Web Solutions** 

#### blockchain engineer

SotaTek is a part of Sota Holdings, a global Software Development as a Service (SDaaS), IT Outsourcing & IT Consulting group. We provide sustainable Software Development (Web/App), Blockchain, AI & Machine Learning, ERP with cost-effective solutions to achieve sustainable growth for enterprises of all sizes. With Software Development & Blockchain Technology as our main expertise, we offer advanced web app, cloud-based solutions for various industries: blockchain apps, cryptocurrency exchange, smart contracts and ICO, allowing your enterprises to leverage the latest technology at ease, to gain competitive advantages and become the leader of your industry. SotaTek stands for "State-of-the-art Technology". We offers dynamic tech experts with strong determination, enthusiasm and commitment in providing the most hi-tech IT services, with the ultimate goal to digital transform and skyrocket our Client's business.

#### core developer

We are a Japanese software company providing Al chatbot tool in Japan and abroad. With our team composed of highly skilled engineers, sales managers and marketers, we are supporting more than 16,000 clients which make us now the No.1 Al chatbot provider in Japan since our launch in 2016. WHAT WE OFFER: Al chatbot with a huge number of customized functions that will definitively make you satisfied. OUR VALUE: Innovation - Customer Satisfaction - Sales Support – Progress - Customized Services WHAT YOU CAN EXPECT: 6 plans to choose from \$14 only One of the cheapest chatbot services on the market without a lack of quality.

#### WEB frontend and backend developer

About the company: We are a Tokyo-based IT firm delivering high quality, cost effective, reliable result-oriented web and e-commerce solutions on time for a global clientele. Professionalism, Skill and Expertise are the tools we use to make the web work for your business bringing in maximum return on your investment in shortest possible time. Web design and online marketing is our forte. Our web solutions aim at enhancing brand awareness, driving performance, attracting potential customers, increasing sales and improving ROI for our clients.

### Education

April 2013 - October 2017 **The University of Tokyo - Bachelor**computer science

We are a Tokyo-based IT firm delivering high quality, cost effective, reliable result-oriented web and e-commerce solutions on time for a global clientele. Professionalism, Skill and Expertise are the tools we use to make the web work for your business bringing in maximum return on your investment in shortest possible time. Web design and online marketing is our forte. Our web solutions aim at enhancing brand awareness, driving performance, attracting potential customers, increasing sales and improving ROI for our clients.

### **Skills**

HTML	6 ye	rears	CSS	6 year	rs
HTML5	4 y	rears	CSS3	4 year	rs
JavaSc ript	6 y	rears	React	4 year	rs
React Native	4 y	ears	Angular	4 year	rs
Angular JS	4 y	rears	Vue	3 year	rs
Next.js	3 y	rears	Nuxt.js	3 year	rs
PHP	4 y	rears	Node.js	4 year	rs
Expres s.js	4 ye	ears	Unity	2 year	rs
Blockc hain	2 y	rears	Rust	1 year	ar
Solidty	2 y	rears	Web3.js	2 year	rs
ether.js	2 y	rears	NFT	2 year	rs
SQL	4 y	rears	Mongo DB	4 year	rs

# Language proficiency